<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-11-21T18:17:17+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">A new beginning</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2021/11/21/a-new-beginning.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A new beginning" /><published>2021-11-21T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2021-11-21T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2021/11/21/a-new-beginning</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2021/11/21/a-new-beginning.html">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first post on this blog, and generally my first blog post in over 2 years!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog replaces &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/lynxmic&quot;&gt;the Medium blog&lt;/a&gt;, which I’ve been using since 2018 up to this point. My perspective on the platform today is no longer the same as when I first joined.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;overhauled-experience&quot;&gt;Overhauled experience&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jekyll is being used this time for the core functionality of the Lynxmic Blog, which is now hosted on GitHub Pages. Consider this my first code project since 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The layout derives from my old personal website (closed in early 2019), and as such uses MDBootstrap (Standard Bootstrap 4 variant), a CSS framework I’ve been using for most of the websites I made. Bootstrap 5 was released in the meantime, and this website uses its icon set (unlike v4, it includes the icon for Discord).Expect further improvements to the blog itself as time passes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;so-the-future-of-the-medium-blog&quot;&gt;So, the future of the Medium blog?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the next few weeks, old posts since 2017 until now will be migrated over to this blog, both from Medium and the older Blogger blog (BriciWorld Blog) which was deleted. I have a backup for the latter, so it’s all set here. After migration of all posts is complete, the Medium blog will be completely phased out.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Lynxmic</name></author><summary type="html">Welcome to the first post on this blog, and generally my first blog post in over 2 years!</summary></entry></feed>